Mmm. Mmm.
Mmm. This cake
is amazing. Mmm.
My God, get a room.
Mmm.
I would get a room
with this cake.
I think I could
show this cake a good time.
If you had to, what would you
give up-- food or sex?
Sex.
Seriously,
answer faster.
Oh, I'm sorry, honey.
No, when she said sex,
I wasn't thinking
about sex with you.
It's like a giant hug.
Ross, how 'bout you?
Which would you give up--
sex or food?
Food.
Okay, how 'bout
sex or dinosaurs?
Oh, my God.
It's like Sophie's Choice.
What about you, Joe?
What would you give
up-- sex or food?
Uh... ooh... uh.
I don't know. It's too hard.
No, you gotta
pick one.
( sighs )
Uh... food.
No, sex.
Food.
Sex.
Food. Se... I don't know.
Oh, God, I want both.
I want... I want girls on bread.
♪ So no one told you
life was gonna be this way ♪
♪ Your job's a joke,
you're broke ♪
♪ Your love life's D.O.A. ♪
♪ It's like you're always
stuck in second gear ♪
♪ When it hasn't been
your day, your week ♪
♪ Your month,
or even your year ♪
♪ But I'll be there for you ♪
♪ 'Cause you're there
for me, too. ♪
Okay, you've
got to see
these latest
pictures of Emma.
Oh, how cute.
Oh, she looks just
like a little doll.
Oh, no, no. That is a doll.
Oh, thank God, 'cause that
thing's really creepy.
Yeah.
Oh, there's Chandler.
Oh. Who's the blonde?
She's pretty.
( gasps ):
He's having
an affair.
He is not having an affair.
You know I'm always right
about these things.
No, you're not.
Last week you thought Ross
was trying to kill you.
Well, I'm sorry,
but it's hard to believe
that anyone would tell a story
that dull just to tell it.
I swear there's something
going on with them. Look.
He's getting into
the car with her.
Oh, that doesn't
mean anything.
Oh, yeah? Well,
let's see.
Huh?
Okay, duck down.
Oh.
( phone ringing )
Hello.
Oh, Hi, Chandler, it's Phoebe.
I know that Monica
is working today
so I was wondering
if you wanted
to come to the movies
with me and Rachel.
Oh, uh... I have to work, too.
Yeah, I'm stuck here
at the office all day.
Uh, well, it's a
shame that you'll,
that you'll
miss the movie
'cause we were
gonna see, you know,
either, um, Liar, Liar
or, um... Betrayal
or An Affair to Remember.
Those are all really old.
Okay, then maybe
it'll be, um...
Dude, Where's My Car?
What?
They're in a car.
Okay, well, all right,
talk to you later.
Okay, 'bye.
Sheesh.
Okay, quick.
We got to find
a cab and follow them.
Oh, yeah, okay,
let me just grab
my night-vision goggles
and my stun gun.
I got 'em.
Hey.
Hey. Hey, sweetie.
Hey, you smell like
perfume and cigarettes.
I was in the car
with Nancy all day.
Nancy doesn't smoke.
Well, at least
the perfume's not mine.
Be thankful for that.
So?
What did you think of the house?
It's perfect. It's everything
we've been looking for.
Isn't it?
And what about the,
the amazing wainscoting
and the crown molding
and the dormer windows
in the attic?
And the wigglewoms
and the zipzorps?
What were
the things you said?
Don't you love the huge yard?
And the fireplace
in the bedroom.
And Nancy said
it's really under-priced
because the guy
lost his job
and has to move in
with his parents.
This is bringing out
a lovely color in you.
So... Do you think
we should get it?
I don't know.
What do you think?
I think we should.
I do, too.
This is huge.
I know.
How bad do you want
to smoke right now?
I don't know what you mean...
giant talking cigarette.
Oh, by the way, Phoebe called
just as I was getting
into Nancy's car,
so if she asks you,
I was at work all day.
Gotcha.
When do we tell them about this?
We don't. Not until
it's a hundred percent.
Why upset everybody
over nothing?
Okay. Right.
Oh, my God,
that is going to be so hard.
I know. Good luck with it.
I just can't
see Chandler cheating.
I'm telling you guys,
we followed them out
to a house in Westchester.
They went in for like 45 minutes
and then they came out
looking pretty happy.
Chandler?
Mm-hmm.
45 minutes?
Well, something's not right.
I just can't believe
he would do this to Monica.
I know and,
and with the baby coming.
So, should we tell her?
I don't know.
Phoebe, if, if one of us
saw Mike with another woman,
would you want us to tell you?
Why, who'd you
see him with?
No one. I'm just
saying, if we...
Tell me what you know!
( shrieking )
Ow. No, nothing.
Mike's a great guy.
It was hypothetical.
All right.
He is a good guy.
You're right.
He wouldn't cheat.
Believe me, if I did
see him with someone,
there's no way I...
Who did you
see him with?!
( shrieking )
( humming )
Oh, look at her.
So happy.
If only there were a smaller one
to clean this one.
Hey, is, uh,
is-is Chandler here?
No, he's picking up dinner.
Why, what's up?
Well...
Look, whatever happens,
we're here for you,
and we love you.
All right.
We think Chandler might
be having an affair.
What?
Phoebe and I saw Chandler
with a blonde woman today
outside on the street
and then we followed them
to a house in Westchester.
They went in together.
So sorry.
Oh, my God.
Oh, my God, that's awful.
What did you think of the house?
What?
Monica, you understand
what we're saying, right?
Yeah. Sure.
And I'm devastated,
obviously.
Did you think
the neighborhood was homey?
All right.
You son of a bitch.
Is it me,
or have the greetings
gone downhill around here?
Phoebe and Rachel
saw you with Nancy today
and, um, they think
you're having an affair.
Rachel, who's Nancy?
What's going on?
Uh... Okay.
All right, guys,
you better sit down.
This is, this
is pretty big.
Yeah.
I'm not having an affair.
Nancy... is our Realtor.
I knew he couldn't be with a
woman for 45 minutes! ( laughs )
I knew it.
Why... w-why
do you have a Realtor?
Um... She's been showing us
houses outside of the city.
What?
Are you serious?
When we found out
that we were going
to get this baby,
Chandler and I
started talking
and we decided
that we didn't want
to raise a kid
in the city.
So you're,
so you're gonna move?
Oh, my God.
Shouldn't we all vote
on stuff like this?
What is wrong with raising
a kid in the city?
I'm doing it.
Ross is doing it.
Sarah Jessica Parker
is doing it.
And that's great
for you guys,
but we want a lawn
and a swing set.
And a street where our
kids can ride their bikes
and maybe an ice cream
truck can go by.
So you want to buy a
house in the '50s.
Have you thought about
what you're giving up?
You can't move out of the city.
What if... what if you want
Chinese food at 5:00 a.m.?
or a fake Rolex that breaks
as soon as it rains?
Or an Asian hooker
sent right to your door?
ROSS:
You know what?
If you want to look
for a house, that's okay.
No, no, it's not.
Don't listen to him.
I'm gonna thump you.
It's okay
because they have
to get it out of their system.
Okay? But,
you're gonna realize,
this is the only place
you want to be.
Actually...
we already found
a house we love.
What?
And about an hour ago,
we made an offer.
Bet you wish
I was having
an affair now, huh?
You put an offer
on a house?
It's so sweet.
It really is.
It has this big yard
that leads down to this stream.
And then there's
these old maple trees.
Oh, again with the nature!
What are you, beavers?
Look, I know this
is really hard, and
we're really sorry.
Is this because I come over here
without knocking
and eat your food?
Because I can stop doing that.
I... I really,
really think I can.
You know that's not
the reason, Joe.
MONICA:
I think if you saw it,
you'd understand.
I mean, you guys were there.
It's-it's beautiful, isn't it?
Yeah, it is.
What the hell
are you doing?!
Well... it is,
all right?
When we were out there today,
all I keep thinking was,
"I can't believe Chandler
is screwing this woman,
but man, this would be
a nice place to live!"
Yeah, but so is this.
Yeah, I mean, if you move there,
you have to leave here.
I mean, how can you leave
this place?
Come on, Daddy,
listen to me!
It's like all of my life,
everyone has always told me,
"You're a shoe!
You're a shoe,
you're a shoe,
you're a shoe!"
And then today,
I just stopped and I said,
"What if I don't want
to be a shoe?
What if I want to be
a-a purse?"
You know, or-or-or a hat?
No, I don't want you
to buy me a hat.
I'm saying that I am a ha...
It's a metaphor, Daddy.
You can see where
he'd have trouble.
Well, maybe I'll just stay here
with Monica.
Well, I guess we've established
who's staying here with Monica.
Your money's mine, Green.
Your fly is open, Geller.
Oh, do you know
what I just realized?
"Joker" is "poker"
with a "J."
Coincidence?
Hey, that's
"Joe-incidence"
with a "c."
Ooh, look!
Ugly Naked Guy lit
a bunch of candles.
ALL:
Ew!
( all gasping )
That had to hurt.
Aw...
Hey, it's your Thanksgiving,
too, you know?
Instead of watching football,
you could help.
GUYS:
We know.
Rachel, you want to put
the marshmallows
in concentric circles.
No, Mon, you want to put them
I want to do this.
Every year.
( gasps )
JOEY:
It's stuck!
Well...
step...
How did it get on?!
I put it on
to scare Chandler.
Oh, my God!
Monica's going to
totally freak out!
Plus, it smells
really bad in here.
Yeah, of course
it smells bad.
You have your head
inside a turkey's ass.
Oh, oh!
Monica.
Oh!
Hey, did you get the turkey...?
Oh, my God!
Who is that?
It's Joey!
I got it.
How 'bout, if we win,
they have to get
rid of the rooster?
Ooh, that's interesting.
If you win, we
give up the bird.
( shudders )
But if we win...
we get your apartment.
( Rachel scoffs )
JOEY:
Ooh-hoo-hoo
hoo-hoo!
Deal!
Wha...?
What?!
What was Monica's nickname when
she was a field hockey goalie?
Big Fat Goalie.
Correct.
Rachel claims this
is her favorite movie.
Dangerous Liaisons.
Correct.
Her actual favorite movie is?
Weekend at Bernie's.
Correct.
Monica categorizes her towels.
How many categories are there?
Okay, Everyday Use.
Fancy.
Guest.
Fancy Guest.
Two seconds.
Ah... eleven?!
11, unbelievable.
11 is correct.
Yes!
( Joey cackles )
Chandler was how old when he
first touched a girl's breast?
Fourteen?
No, 19.
Thanks, man.
Joey had
an imaginary childhood friend.
His name was?
Maurice.
Correct.
His profession was...?
Oh, space cowboy!
Correct.
What is Chandler Bing's job?
Uh...
Oh...
Oh, gosh.
Ten seconds. You need this,
or you lose the game.
Oh!
It's, um...
it has something
to do with transponding...
Oh, oh, oh, he's
a transpons...
transponster!
That's not even a word!
Oh!
No, I-I...
Oh, my...
Noooooo...!
( chuckles )
RACHEL:
You know what?
You are mean boys
who are just being mean.
Hey, don't get mad at us.
No one forced you
to raise the stakes.
That is not true.
She did.
She forced me.
Hey, we'd still
be living here,
if you hadn't gotten
the question wrong.
Well, it was a stupid,
unfair question.
Don't blame the questions.
Would you all stop yelling
in our apartment?
You are ruining
moving day for us.
Chandler!
I saw what you were doing
through the window!
to my sister.
Now, get out here!
Listen, we had a good run.
You know, what was it?
Four-five months?
I mean, that's more than most
people have in a lifetime,
so good-bye, take care,
bye-bye, then.
Hey, Ross.
What's up, bro?
What...
the hell are you doing?!
Hey, wh-what's going on?
Well, I think-- I think--
Ross knows about
me and Monica.
( half-whispers ):
Dude, he's right there...
I thought you were
my best friend.
This is my sister.
My best friend and my sister--
I-I cannot believe this.
Look, we're not
just messing around.
I love her, okay?
I'm in love with her.
I am so sorry that you had
to find out this way.
I'm sorry, but it's true.
I-I love him, too.
My best friend and my sister!
I cannot believe this!
Well, this is the last
box of your clothes.
I'm just gonna label it
"What were you thinking?"
Funny, 'cause I was just gonna
go across the hall
and write that on Chandler.
Okay, you guys, I don't mean
to make things worse,
but, um... I don't want to live
with Rachel anymore.
What?!
You're just
so mean to
each other.
And I don't want to end up
like that with Rachel.
I still like you.
Well, Phoebe, that's fine,
because I'm not moving.
Whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa.
Phoebe, you gotta take her.
You know, I know I said
some really bad stuff about her,
but you know, Rachel does have
some good qualities
that make her a good roommate.
She gets tons of catalogs.
And she'll fold down the pages
of the things
that she thinks that I'd like.
What else?
Well...
When I take a shower,
she leaves me little notes
on the mirror.
Yeah, I do.
I do do that.
That's nice.
I like having things to read
in the bathroom.
When I fall asleep
on the couch
after reading,
she covers me over
with a blanket.
Well, you know,
I don't want you to be cold.
And...
when I told her that I was going
to be moving in with Chandler,
she was really supportive.
( voice breaking ):
You were so great.
You made it so easy.
( sobbing ):
And now you
have to leave...
and I have to
live with a boy!
Oh...
honey!
Hey.
She really left.
Yeah, I know.
Thank you.
No problem, roomie.
Thanks.
Can I ask you a question?
Sure.
What the hell is
that dog doing here?
Little toast here.
Ding-ding...
I know this isn't exactly
the kind of Thanksgiving
that all of you planned,
but for me, this has been
really great, you know?
I think because
it didn't involve divorce
or projectile vomiting.
Anyway, I was just thinking,
I mean, if you'd gone to Vail,
or if you guys had been
with your family,
or if you didn't have...
syphilis and stuff...
...we wouldn't be all together,
you know?
So, I guess what I'm trying
to say is
that I'm very thankful
that all of
your Thanksgivings sucked.
That's so sweet.
Thank you...
Mmm!
And, hey, here's to
a lousy Christmas.
And a crappy New Year.
Hear, hear!
You can't move.
You just... you just can't.
Rachel's right.
This is where you guys belong.
Yeah, you don't want
to live in Westchester.
That's like the worst
of the Chesters.
ROSS:
You know,
sometimes,
when I'm alone in my apartment,
I look over here,
and you guys are
just having dinner
or watching TV
or something, but...
it makes me feel better.
And now when I
look over, who
am I gonna see?
The Gottliebs?
The Yangs?
They don't make
me feel so good.
Yeah, so-so
don't move, okay?
Just stay here, and...
maybe close
your blinds at night.
Hey.
( phone rings )
( sighs )
Hello?
It's Nancy.
They responded to our offer.
And?
Okay, thanks.
They passed.
They said they wouldn't go
a penny under the asking price.
We can't afford that.
I know.
Well, there you go.
JOEY:
I'm really
sorry, you guys.
Yeah, I'm sorry, too.
I'm even more sorry
that that phone call
didn't come
before I told you
about looking through
the window.
RACHEL:
Yeah, well,
we're going
to let you be alone.
You going to be okay?
Yeah, we'll be okay.
I love you guys.
Hey, you know,
I'm really sorry I wasn't
more supportive before.
Oh, it's okay.
We understand.
Yeah, and about this Nancy...
if you're not sleeping
with her, should I?
I know there'll be other houses,
but I just...
I love that one so much.
Yeah.
Well, it's a good thing
we got it, then.
What?!
We got the house!
Oh, my God!
I just didn't want to tell you
in front of them.
Oh, my God! We got it?
We got the house?!
We're getting the house!
Oh!
Mmm!
We're getting a house.
And a baby!
We're growing up.
We sure are.
So, who's gonna tell them?
Not it!
Not it.
Damn it!
And Rachel,
this is yours.
( screams ):
What are these for?!
You'll see.
All right.
Everybody
open them.
Okay.
( gasps )
Oh, wow, this
is so beautiful!
Oh, these are the ones
I was looking at in the store.
I know.
I love this.
A meatball sub!?
Thanks!
Seriously, you guys.
What's going on?
What are these for?
Well, I didn't know
how to tell you before, but...
we got the house.
Enjoy!
Captioned by
Media Access Group at WGBH
access.wgbh.org
What did they say?